Privacy and security center
===========================

At Edward Jones, we work to earn your trust every day by safeguarding your personal information.

What we do to help protect you
------------------------------

Our success depends on your success. That’s why we work to prevent attempted attacks on the systems that hold your information. But we also prepare for the worst, training to respond to incidents and conduct business as usual.

Learn more about our strategies to help protect your assets and information.

Learn more about our efforts to remain resilient and deliver the service you expect.

What you can do to help protect yourself
----------------------------------------

Anyone can become a victim of fraud. Knowing about scams and how they operate can help you identify and avoid them.

Learn how to spot scams before they affect you.

Being proactive could save you time and money.

Our privacy principles
----------------------

* We tell you how we will collect, maintain and use your information, and then we use it only for those purposes.
* Only employees who need to know your information can access it.
* We do our best to keep your information accurate and complete.

Learn more: [Read the full Edward Jones Privacy Notice](https://www.edwardjones.com/sites/default/files/acquiadam/2023-03/privacy-notice.pdf "Edward Jones Privacy Policy PDF") (PDF).

### California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA)

The California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA) provides California residents with specific rights regarding how their personal information is collected and maintained, [which is more fully explained in our California Privacy Notice](https://www.edwardjones.com/us-en/privacy/california-privacy-notice "California Privacy Notice"). 

### Oregon Consumer Privacy Act

The Oregon Consumer Privacy Act provides Oregon residents with specific rights regarding how their personal information is collected and maintained.

### Consumer Data Rights Request

[Use our portal](https://privacyportal.onetrust.com/webform/72962654-4344-4857-b8ef-0b74022632d7/cd516469-d0ab-4ee6-812c-631a7b239556), powered by OneTrust, to submit a consumer data rights request to the Edward Jones Privacy team. For questions, contact the Privacy team at 855-898-6102 or [\[email protected\]](https://www.edwardjones.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

Learn what you can do if you suspect you’re a victim of fraud.
--------------------------------------------------------------

### Explore our Privacy and Security Center

* 

* 

* 

* 

* 

* 

Back to Top

Follow us to stay up to date
----------------------------

Copyright © 2024 Edward Jones. All rights reserved. Member [SIPC](https://www.sipc.org/). 

This site is designed for U.S. residents only. The services offered within this site are available exclusively through our U.S. financial advisors. Edward Jones' U.S. financial advisors may only conduct business with residents of the states for which they are properly registered. Please note that not all of the investments and services mentioned are available in every state.
